GTFO

Privacy Policy

Last Updated: 3 November 2023

Thank you for using our products and services! We respect your concerns about privacy and appreciate

your trust and confidence in us.

Here is a summary of the information contained in this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”). This summary

is to help you navigate the Privacy Policy and it is not a substitute for reading everything! You can use

the hyperlinks below to jump directly to particular sections.

What information do we need to provide the Game

If you register an account to use the Game then we will need some information from you to set this up.

If you choose, you can provide certain other information to personalise your experience of the Game,

enable Game features or participate in the Game. If you need to get in touch with us, we will retain

some information so that we can get back in touch with you and address any concerns. More

Information.

How will we use your information?

We use your information to provide the many functions and services that comprise the Game. We also

use your information for account verification and to support and improve the Game. We do not share

your information with any third parties, except where we need to in order to provide the Game (e.g., if

you choose, you can record data on online community platforms or to back up your data; use our

affiliates around the world to help us to deliver the Game) or monitor the success of our marketing and

advertising programs, or where we are instructed to by a court, authority or compelled by law. More

Information.

Who do we share your information with?

We use some third parties to help us deliver the best possible experience (e.g., cloud services to back

up your data and support services, analytics providers to carry out data analytics). When we use a third

party, we only do this to process or store your information for the purposes described in this Privacy

Policy. We also have affiliates around the world who help us deliver the Game and we may be required

by a court or legal obligation to disclose certain information in some circumstances. More Information.

Where do we process your information?

Our servers are located in Sweden. Your information can be accessed from outside of where you live

by our support, engineering and other teams around the world, including Sweden and the United

States. More Information.

How long do we keep hold of your information?

We generally retain your information for the period during which you maintain an account for the

Game, or until account deletion in accordance with your request, after which your data is deleted (as

further described in this Privacy Policy), unless otherwise required by applicable laws. More

Information.

How can I exercise my rights over my information?

Depending on where you are, you may have certain rights with respect to your information, such as

rights of access, to receive a copy of your data, or to delete your data or restrict or object to our

processing of your data. More Information.

How to get in touch with us

If you have any questions about anything in this Privacy Policy, or want to exercise any rights you may

have, please contact us here.

How will we notify you of changes?

Changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted here. Please check this page frequently to see if there are

any updates or changes to this Privacy Policy. More Information.

Contact Information

Data Controller: 10 Chambers AB Email: privacy@10chambers.com

Welcome to GTFO!

This Privacy Policy explains the when, how and why when it comes to the processing of your personal

information in connection with GTFO (the “Game”) and sets out your choices and rights in relation to

that information. Please read it carefully – it is important for you to understand how we collect and

use your information, and how you can control it.

If you do not agree to the processing of your personal information in the way this Privacy Policy

describes, please do not provide your information when requested and stop using the Game. By

using the Game you are acknowledging our rules regarding your personal information as described

in this Privacy Policy.

This Game has been developed by 10 Chambers AB (“we”, “us”, “our”).

For the purpose of data protection laws, the data controller of your personal information in relation

to the Game is 10 Chambers AB. The registered address of 10 Chambers AB is Drottninggatan 95A, 113

60 Stockholm, Sweden.

Please reach out to us if you have any questions or concerns regarding the processing of your personal

information. You can contact us anytime at privacy@10chambers.com.

1. The Types of Personal Information We Use

This section describes the different types of personal information we collect from you and how we

collect it. If you would like to know more about specific types of data and how we use that data, please

see the section entitled “How We Use Your Personal Information” below.

The following is a high-level summary of the types of personal information we use:

1\. Information you provide to us (either directly or through a third party).

• Account registration information: You give us information about you when you set up an

account to register for the Game: information we import from your connected Steam account

in order to set up your profile, including your name as it appears on Steam and your Steam ID.

• Customer support and feedback information: Email address and the content of your support

request.

• Email address: If you provide us your email address to receive newsletters with your consent.

2\. Information about you generated as part of the Game

We automatically collect certain data from you when you use the Game, namely:

• your Game data, including PlayFab ID, game data including login information, game play

information; IP address, device information, including device ID, platform and information

regarding your use of the Game, such as play statistics (e.g. level and scores);

• each time you interact with us, for example, if you contact our support team, we collect

information including your email and the content disclosed in the email;

• information regarding your engagement with our advertising efforts, including technical

identifiers, location, communication data, metadata and Cookie ID;

• information to analyse the performance of our marketing efforts and the Game, including your

IP address, sales and usage data, technical information, technical identifiers, engagement

information and contact information.

2. Cookies

We use cookies and other similar technologies (e.g. web beacons, log files, scripts and eTags)

(“Cookies”) to enhance your experience using the Game. Cookies are small files which, when placed

on your device, enable us to provide certain features and functionalities.

For more information about our Cookies policy, click here.

3. Children

Children must not use the Game for any purpose, except where their parent or guardian has provided

consent (to the extent this option is available in your jurisdiction).

By children, we mean users under the age of 18 years old; or in the case of a region where the

minimum age for processing personal information differs, such different age. For users located in

certain regions we have listed the relevant minimum age in the table below.

Region in which the user is located Minimum age of the user

Australia 18

European Economic Area (Germany and France only) 16

Japan 18

Republic of Korea 14

United Kingdom 13

United States 13

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under these ages for any purpose. If

you believe that we have personal information of a child under these ages without parental/guardian

consent, or if you are the parent or guardian of the user and wish to withdraw consent, please contact

us at privacy@10chambers.com and we will delete such information.

4. How We Use Your Personal Information

This section provides more detail on the types of personal information we collect from you, and why.

For users who live in the United Kingdom, Germany or France (“Relevant Jurisdiction”), it also

identifies the legal basis under which we process your data.

Personal Information Use Legal Basis (only relevant if

you are located in a

Relevant Jurisdiction)

Information you provide to us (either directly or through a third party)

Account Creation: Steam ID,

Steam username, PlayFab ID,

hashed IP address, city,

country.

We use this information to create

and verify your account for the

Game, and to allow you to log in,

in accordance with your request.

Necessary to perform our

contract with you to provide

the Game.

Friend’s Lists: Steam ID, Playfab

ID,

We use this information to

improve the functionality of our

game by seeing who is playing

GTFO.

It is in our legitimate

interest to use this

information to improve the

functionality of our game.

Information generated as part of the Game

Game data including login

information (Microsoft Azure

PlayFab): Steam ID, Steam

nickname, IP address, city and

country, game play data, levels,

scores, completion of game,

vanity items

We use this information to

provide you with feedback and

information about your gameplay

and progress.

Necessary to perform our

contract with you to provide

the Game.

Game data including login

information (Unity Analytics):

Unity User ID (an anonymized

ID), country and city, actions

taken within game, play session

information, operating system,

Unity Player and Unity editor

versions, app ID of game

installed

We use this information for

analytics purposes.

It is in our legitimate

interest to use this

information to conduct data

analytics to further develop

and improve the Game.

Game data and login

information (Unity Cloud

Diagnostics): operating system

and version, CPU, graphic card

information, system language,

device manufacture and model,

RAM, Unity Player and Unity

Editor versions, app ID of game,

screen resolution

We use this information for

diagnostics purposes.

It is in our legitimate

interest to use this

information for diagnostic

purposes for crash and

exception reporting in order

to ensure the functionality

of the Game.

Game and login data Game

Analytics): operating system,

platform (steam), timestart,

game play data such as levels,

scores, actions within the

game, play session information,

vanity items, voice language

chosen for matchmaking

We use this information for

analytics purposes.

It is in our legitimate

interest to use this

information to conduct data

analytics to further develop

and improve the game.

Advertising and marketing

campaigns: technical

identifiers, location,

communication data,

metadata, Cookie ID, IP-

address, mobile device ID, ISP

ID, device type, operating

system and version, browser

and version, referrer URL, site

visit data

We use this information to

monitor our advertising and

marketing campaigns.

We use this information

with your consent.

Chat Data and Game Status:

Free Chat (users can

communicate using their own,

custom messages) and audio

chat (for users located in the

EEA or Switzerland, both chat

functions are only available to

users over the age of 16)

Please note that this data is

only stored on your device and

is not processed by our servers

We facilitate the posting of your

communications and sharing of

your in-game status with other

users.

Necessary to perform our

contract with you to provide

chat functionality within the

Game.

Customer support: email

address and the content of your

support request

We use this information to:

• improve our services; and

• provide troubleshooting, such

as addressing and remediating

technical issues and bugs.

Necessary to perform our

contract with you to provide

and support the Game.

Newsletter: email address We use this information to

provide you with our newsletter.

We use this information

with your consent.

Marketing analytics data

(Google Analytics): Technical

information and identifiers,

engagement information and

contact information

We use this information to

monitor the success of our

advertising and marketing

programs. If you click on a link or

interact with content that

advertises the Game, we store

certain marketing analytics data

with your profile.

We use this information

with your consent.

Marketing (social media):

social media user account

information and comments

from such accounts on our

social media content

We use this information to

centrally manage our social media

platforms.

We use this information

with your consent.

Marketing analytics data: IP

address, sales and usage data

(i.e., information about how

This information is used to create

a fingerprint. Fingerprints are built

We use this information

with your consent.

data subject interacts with the

game and marketing activities)

and hashed into an anonymous

identifier.

We use this information to

monitor the success of our

advertising and marketing

programs.

Marketing attribution data: IP

address, anonymized user ID,

timestamp, OS version, screen

resolution, time-zone, system

language, and in-game events,

Steam platform data

We use this information to

analyse the performance of our

marketing efforts and the Game.

We use this information

with your consent.

5. How We Store and Share Your Personal Information

Our corporate group operates around the world. Pursuant to our contract with you to provide you

with the Game, your personal information will be processed on servers that may not be located where

you live. No matter where our servers are located, we take appropriate measures to safeguard your

rights in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Our servers for the Game are located in Sweden. We also

have support, engineering and other teams who may support the Game including from Sweden and

the United States.

Only where necessary will we share your personal information with third parties. Situations where

this occur are:

• Third parties that provide services in support of the Game, including providers for the purpose

of processing support ticket ID and support communication, managing our social media

platforms, processing gameplay and game rendering data to provide game analytics to

improve gameplay, and for the purpose of providing marketing and advertisements and

monitor the success of our marketing and advertising programs. All companies providing

services for us are prohibited from retaining, using, or disclosing your personal information

for any purpose other than providing us with their services.

• Companies within our corporate group who process your personal information in order to

operate the Game. All related group companies may only use your personal information in

accordance with this Privacy Policy.

• Regulators, judicial authorities and law enforcement agencies, and other third parties for

safety, security, or compliance with the law. There are circumstances in which we are legally

required to disclose information about you to authorities, such as to comply with a legal

obligation or processes, enforce our terms, address issues relating to security or fraud, or

protect our users. These disclosures may be made with or without your consent, and with or

without notice, in compliance with the terms of valid legal process such as a subpoena, court

order, or search warrant. We are usually prohibited from notifying you of any such disclosures

by the terms of the legal process. We may seek your consent to disclose information in

response to a governmental entity’s request when that governmental entity has not provided

the required subpoena, court order, or search warrant. We may also disclose your information

to:

o enforce our terms and conditions and other agreements, including investigation of

any potential violation thereof;

o detect, prevent or otherwise address security, fraud or technical issues; or

o protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users, a third party or the public as

required or permitted by law (exchanging information with other companies and

organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction).

• A third party that acquires all or substantially all of us or our business. We may also disclose

your information to third parties if we either: (a) sell, transfer, merge, consolidate or re-

organise any part(s) of our business, or merge with, acquire or form a joint venture with, any

other business, in which case we may disclose your data to any prospective buyer, new owner,

or other third party involved in such change to our business; or (b) sell or transfer any of our

assets, in which case the information we hold about you may be sold as part of those assets

and may be transferred to any prospective buyer, new owner, or other third party involved in

such sale or transfer.

6. The Security of Your Personal Information

We are committed to maintaining the privacy and integrity of your personal information no matter

where it is stored. We have information security and access policies that limit access to our systems

and technology, and we protect data through the use of technological protection measures such as

encryption.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we

will implement and maintain reasonable measures to protect your personal information, we cannot

guarantee the security of the information transmitted through the Game or otherwise via the Internet;

any transmission is at your own risk.

7. Data Retention

We do not keep your data for longer than is necessary unless we are required to do so under law. For

further details on how long we keep your data, please refer to the time periods set out below.

Personal Information Retention Policy

Steam ID, Steam username, PlayFab ID, city,

country

Stored for the lifetime of your use of the Game

(i.e. until account deletion in accordance with

your request upon which it will be deleted

within 30 working days).Game data and play statistics (Microsoft Azure

PlayFab, Unity Analytics, Unity Cloud Diagnostics,

Discord)

Advertising and marketing campaigns

Marketing analytics data

Customer support data

Marketing (social media) information

Marketing (technical data) information

Steam friends lists This data is not permanently stored and is only

processed for matchmaking purposes.

Chat Data This data is not permanently stored on servers,

and is only processed to ensure messages are

delivered to your device. All chat data is

thereafter only stored on your device.

Newsletter Until unsubscribing from the newsletter upon

which the information will be deleted within

30 working days or otherwise stored for the

lifetime of your use of the Game (i.e. until

account deletion in accordance with your

request upon which it will be deleted within

30 working days).

Marketing attribution information Stored for 14 months, or deleted within 30

working days upon your account deletion

request.

If we are required to retain your information beyond the retention periods set out above, for example

to comply with applicable laws, we will store it separately from other types of personal information.

8. Your Rights

Some jurisdictions’ laws grant specific rights to users of the Game, which are set out in this section.

This section entitled “Your Rights” applies to users that are located in the Relevant Jurisdictions. If

you are located in a territory outside a Relevant Jurisdiction, please refer to the Supplemental

Jurisdiction-Specific Terms for an overview of your rights and how these can be exercised.

The sub-section entitled “Advertising” also apply to users that are located in Japan, Korea, United

States and Australia.

You have certain rights in relation to the personal information we hold about you, depending on where

you are located. Some of these only apply in certain circumstances (as set out in more detail below).

We must respond to a request by you to exercise those rights without undue delay and at least within

one month (though this may be extended by a further two months in certain circumstances). To

exercise any of your rights, please contact us at privacy@10chambers.com.

Access

You have the right to access personal information we hold about you, how we use it, and who we

share it with. You can access the personal information you have made available as part of your account

by logging into your account. If you believe we hold any other personal information about you, please

contact us at privacy@10chambers.com.

Portability

You have the right to receive a copy of certain personal information we process about you. This

comprises any personal information we process on the basis of your consent (e.g., information

collected to provide our newsletter) or pursuant to our contract with you (e.g., account name), as

described above in the section “How We Use Your Personal Information”. You have the right to receive

this information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. You also have the right

to request that we transfer that personal information to another party, with certain exceptions. We

will provide further information to you about this if you make such a request.

If you wish for us to transfer such personal information to a third party, please ensure you detail that

party in your request. Note that we can only do so where it is technically feasible. Please note that we

may not be able to provide you with personal information if providing it would interfere with another’s

rights (for example, where providing the personal information we hold about you would reveal

information about another person or our trade secrets or intellectual property).

Correction

You have the right to correct any of your personal information we hold that is inaccurate. You can

access the personal information we hold about you by logging into your Game account. If you believe

we hold any other personal information about you and that information is inaccurate, please contact

us at privacy@10chambers.com.

Erasure

You can delete your account, or remove certain personal information, by logging into your Game

account. If there is any other personal information you believe we process that you would like us to

erase, please contact us at privacy@10chambers.com.

We may need to retain personal information if there are valid grounds under data protection laws for

us to do so (for example, for the defence of legal claims or freedom of expression) but we will let you

know if that is the case. Where you have requested that we erase personal information that has been

made available publicly on the Game and there are grounds for erasure, we will use reasonable steps

to try to tell others that are displaying the personal information or providing links to the personal

information to erase it too.

Restriction of Processing to Storage Only

You have a right to require us to stop processing the personal information we hold about you other

than for storage purposes in certain circumstances. Please note, however, that if we stop processing

the personal information, we may use it again if there are valid grounds under data protection laws

for us to do so (for example, for the defence of legal claims or for another’s protection). As above,

where we agree to stop processing the personal information, we will try to tell any third party to whom

we have disclosed the relevant personal information so that they can stop processing it too.

Objection

You have the right to object to our processing of your personal information. We will consider your

request in other circumstances as detailed below by contacting us at privacy@10chambers.com.

To the extent provided by applicable laws and regulations, you may withdraw any consent you

previously provided to us for certain processing activities by contacting us at

privacy@10chambers.com. Where consent is required to process your personal information, if you do

not consent to the processing or if you withdraw your consent we may not be able to deliver the

expected service.

Announcements

We may from time to time send you announcements when we consider it necessary to do so (for

example, when we temporarily suspend access to the Game for maintenance, or security, privacy or

administrative-related communications). You may not opt-out of these service-related

announcements, which are not promotional in nature.

Advertising

You may choose to stop receiving personalised advertising or marketing promotions from us when

using the Game by contacting us at privacy@10chambers.com.

9. Contact \& Complaints

Any questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy should be addressed to

privacy@10chambers.com.

In the event that you wish to make a complaint about how we process your personal information,

please contact us in the first instance at privacy@10chambers.com and we will endeavour to deal

with your request as soon as possible. This is without prejudice to your right to launch a claim with

the data protection authority in the region in which you live or work where you think we have

infringed data protection laws.

10. Changes

If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy we will post the updated Privacy Policy here. Please

check this page frequently to see if there are any updates or changes to this Privacy Policy.

11. Language

Except as otherwise prescribed by law, in the event of any discrepancy or inconsistency between the

English version and local language version of this privacy policy, the English version shall prevail.

INFORMATION FOR PARENTS

Before your child can play the Game, you will need to provide your consent to approve your child’s

account set-up and the processing of their personal information.

What personal information does the Game process?

The Game is a survival first-person cooperative game.

If your child successfully signs up to the Game, this will result in the collection and sharing of certain

personal information:

• Steam ID, Steam username, PlayFab ID, hashed IP address, city, country;

• Game data, including login information (Microsoft Azure PlayFab): such as Steam ID, Steam

nickname, IP address, city and country;

• Game data including login information (Unity Analytics): such as Unity User ID (an

anonymized ID), country and city, actions taken within game, play session information;

• Game data and login information (Unity Cloud Diagnostics): such as operating system and

version, CPU, graphic card information, system language, device information;

• Advertising and marketing campaigns: such as technical identifiers, location, communication

data, metadata, Cookie ID, IP-address;

• Chat data;

• Customer support data: email address and content of support request;

• Newsletter data: email address;

• Marketing analytics data (Google Analytics): technical information and identifiers,

engagement information and contact information;

• Marketing (social media): social media user account information and comments from such

accounts on our social media content;

• Marketing analytics data: IP address, sales and usage data; and

• Marketing attribution data: IP address, anonymized user ID, timestamp, OS version, screen

resolution, time-zone, system language, and in-game events, Steam platform data.

You can review our Privacy Policy for more details on what personal information we collect and how

we use and process the information.

Why is my consent required?

Certain jurisdictions require or recommend the consent of a parent or legal guardian before their child

can sign up to a game such as the Game, where personal information will be processed. If you do not

consent, or withdraw your consent, we will immediately delete any personal information collected up

to that point.

What if there are changes to the Game in the future?

If we make any changes to the way their personal information is processed, we will notify you of those

changes. You must consent to those changes before your child’s personal information will be

processed for that new purpose.

Will you retain my personal information?

We will keep a record of your email address so that we can notify you of any changes to the processing

of your child’s personal information, and so that we know you are a parent or legal guardian of a player

when you contact us. As mentioned above, your credit card information is not processed by us, but

instead only processed by a third party payment processor. We do not have access to your credit card

information.

What if I do not consent?

If you do not consent (including by providing your credit card details for verification) then your contact

information will be deleted.

How do I withdraw my consent or delete my child’s account?

You can withdraw your consent or delete your child’s account by emailing us at

privacy@10chambers.com. You can also request a copy of your child’s personal information at any

time.

SUPPLEMENTAL TERMS – JURISDICTION-SPECIFIC

Some jurisdictions’ laws contain additional terms for users of the Game, which are set out in this

section.

If you are a user located in one of the jurisdictions below, the terms set out below under the name

of your jurisdiction apply to you in addition to the terms set out in our Privacy Policy above.

Australia

We take reasonable steps to ensure that third party recipients of your personal information located

outside Australia handle your personal information in a manner that is consistent with Australian

privacy laws. However, you acknowledge that we do not control, or accept liability for, the acts and

omissions of these third party recipients.

You have the right to access personal information we hold about you, how we use it, and who we

share it with. You have the right to correct any of your personal information we hold that is inaccurate.

If you are under the age of 18, you undertake that you have the consent of your parent or legal

guardian to register an account on and use the Game.

Where practicable, we will give you the option of not identifying yourself or using a pseudonym when

registering an account on or using the Game. You acknowledge that if you do not provide us with your

personal information, we may be unable to provide you with access to certain features or sections of

the Game, including social media integration and in-Game purchases.

If you are dissatisfied with our response to your request for access to, or correction of, your personal

information or your privacy complaint in respect of your personal information, you may contact the

Office of the Australian Information Commissioner (Telephone: +61 1300 363 992 or email:

enquiries@oaic.gov.au).

California

This section applies to California residents covered by the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018

(“CCPA”).

Collection and Disclosure of Personal Information

Over the past 12 months, we have collected and disclosed the following categories of personal

information from or about you or your device:

• Identifiers, such as login information, PlayFab ID, IP address, device ID, device token, email

address, and nickname. This information is collected directly from you and your device and

from social media platforms if you choose to sign up using a social media account (Steam).

• Internet or other electronic network activity information, such as your information regarding

your use of the Game, date and time stamps of actions, log-in and clickstream data and other

device Information as described in the main Privacy Policy. This information is collected

directly from you and your device.

• Customer support data.

• Marketing, analytics and ad attribution data.

• Other information described in subdivision (e) of Section 1798.80, including information about

your gender, nationality, or age. This information is collected directly from you in the context

of being our consumer.

We collect your personal information for the following purposes:

• To provide you with the Game, maintain your account and provide customer services.

• To improve our services, including the functionality of the Game.

• To carry out analytics and measure our marketing efforts.

For additional information about what each type of personal information is used for, see Section 4

How We Use Your Personal Information.

We disclose personal information to the following types of entities:

• Other companies within our corporate group who process your personal information in order

to operate the Game.

• Other companies that provide services on our behalf in support of the Game and who are

prohibited by contract from retaining, using, or disclosing personal information for any

purpose other than for providing their services to us.

• Regulators, judicial authorities and law enforcement agencies

• Entities that acquire all or substantially all of our business.

In the past 12 months, we have not sold Personal Information of California residents within the

meaning of “sold” in the CCPA.

Rights under the CCPA:

If you are a California resident, you have the right to:

• Request we disclose to you free of charge the following information covering the 12 months

preceding your request:

o the categories of personal information about you that we collected;

o the categories of sources from which the personal information was collected;

o the purpose for collecting personal information about you;

o the categories of third parties to whom we disclosed personal information about you

and the categories of personal information that was disclosed (if applicable) and the

purpose for disclosing the personal information about you; and

o the specific pieces of personal information we collected about you;

• Request we delete personal information we collected from you, unless CCPA recognises an

exception; and

• Be free from unlawful discrimination for exercising your rights including providing a different

level or quality of services or denying goods or services to you when you exercise your rights

under the CCPA.

We aim to fulfil all verified requests within 45 days pursuant to the CCPA. If necessary, extensions for

an additional 45 days will be accompanied by an explanation for the delay.

How to Exercise Your Rights

First, you may wish to log into your account and manage your data from there. If you are a California

resident to whom the CCPA applies, you may also exercise your rights, if any, regarding other data by

contacting us at privacy@10chambers.com.

Japan

If you are under the age of 18, you must obtain your parent’s or legal guardian’s consent to register

an account on and use the Game.

By clicking “accept”, you consent to the transfer of your personal information to third parties (if any),

which may include the cross-border transfer of your information to any country where we have

databases or affiliates and, in particular, to the jurisdictions specified in Section 5 How We Store and

Share Your Personal Information.

The categories of personal information specified to the jurisdictions in Section 5 How We Store and

Share Your Personal Information may include "special care-required personal information" (i.e.,

sensitive information as detailed under applicable law), and you consent to the collection of such

information.

You may request us to notify you about the purposes of use of, to disclose, to make any correction to,

to discontinue the use or provision of, and/or to delete any and all of your personal information which

is stored by us, to the extent provided by the Act on the Protection of Personal Information of Japan.

When you wish to make such requests, please contact us at privacy@10chambers.com.

Republic of Korea

Provision of personal information to third parties

We provide your personal information to third parties as described below:

Name of Recipient (and contact

information)

Types of Personal

Information provided

Purpose of Use

by Recipient

Period of

Retention and

Use by

Recipient

Microsoft Azure PlayFab

(https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-

us/privacystatement)

Steam ID, Steam

username, PlayFab ID,

city and country, IP

address (partially

disguised), gameplay

data, levels, scores, game

status, items

For account

creation,

verification and

log-in.

To process Game

data.

In accordance

with the

Microsoft

Azure PlayFab

privacy policy.

Google Analytics

(https://policies.google.com/privacy)

Technical information,

technical identifiers,

engagement information

and contact information.

To monitor the

success of our

advertising

campaigns.

In accordance

with the

Google

Developer

License

Agreement and

privacy policy.

Omnicom Media Group AB (OMD)

(https://omnicommediagroup.com/privac

y-notice/)

Technical identifiers,

location, communication

data, metadata, Cookie

ID, IP-address, mobile

device ID, ISP ID, device

type, operating system

and version, browser and

version, referrer URL, site

For advertising

purposes. In accordance

with the

Omnicom

Media Group

AB privacy

policy

visit data

Unity Analytics

(https://unity3d.com/legal/privacy-policy)

Unity User ID (an

anonymized ID), country

and city, actions taken

within game, play session

information, operating

system, Unity Player and

Unity editor versions,

app ID of game

To carry out data

analytics. In accordance

with the Unity

Analytics

privacy policy.

Unity Cloud Diagnostics

(https://unity3d.com/legal/privacy-policy)

Operating system and

version, CPU, graphic

card information, system

language, device model,

RAM, Unity Player and

Unity Editor versions,

app ID of game, screen

resolution

For diagnostics

purposes and to

ensure the

functionality of

the Game.

In accordance

with the Unity

Cloud

Diagnostics

privacy policy.

Mailchimp

(https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)

Email address, service

usage data such as IP

address, operating

system, browser ID,

viewfinder size, system

and connection

information, log data and

usage data, demographic

information, device

information, location and

online engagement data

For sending

newsletters. In accordance

with the

Mailchimp

privacy policy

Hootsuite

(https://www.hootsuite.com/legal/genera

l-data-protection-regulation)

Name, photos, age,

gender, geographic

location, opinions,

preferences, and phone

numbers that are

provided or posted by

social media users.

To manage social

media platforms

centrally.

In accordance

with the

Hootsuite

privacy policy

GameSight

(https://console.gamesight.io/privacy-

policy)

Marketing attribution

data

To analyze the

performance and

marketing efforts

of the Game.

In accordance

with the

GameSight

privacy policy

Overseas Transfer of Personal Information

We transfer personal information to third parties overseas as follows:

Recipient (Contact

Information of

Information

Manager)

Country to

which Your

Personal

Information

is to be

Transferred

Date and

Method of

Transfer

Types of Your

Personal

Information to

be Transferred

Purposes of

Use by

Recipients

Period of

Retention of

Use by

Recipient

Microsoft Azure

PlayFab

(https://privacy.micr

osoft.com/en-

us/privacystatement)

United

States

Transmitted

from time to

time

Steam

nickname and

Steam ID

For account

creation,

verification and

log-in.

To process

Game data.

In accordance

with the

Microsoft

Azure PlayFab

terms

Google Analytics

(https://policies.goog

le.com/privacy)

(United States unless

otherwise described

in the service

provider’s privacy

policy)

United

States

Transmitted

from time to

time

Engagement

data, including

watching

action,

activeness, log

in status will be

transferred to

Google for

targeting

marketing

campaigns

Ad ID

To monitor the

success of our

advertising

campaigns.

In accordance

with the Google

Analytics terms

Omnicom Media

Group AB (OMD)

(https://omnicomme

diagroup.com/privac

y-notice/) United

States

Transmitted

from time to

time

Site visit data

from

10Chambers

website: cookie

ID, IP-address,

mobile device

ID, ISP ID,

device type,

operating

system and

version,

browser and

version,

referrer URL,

email address

For advertising

purposes. In accordance

with the OMD

terms

Mailchimp

(https://mailchimp.c

om/legal/privacy/) United

States

Transmitted

from time to

time

Email address For sending.

Newsletters. In accordance

with the

Mailchimp

terms

Unity Analytics

(https://unity3d.com

/legal/privacy-policy)

United

States

Transmitted

from time to

time

Unity User ID

(an anonymized

ID), country and

city, actions

taken within

game, play

session

information,

operating

system, Unity

Player and

Unity editor

versions, app ID

of game

To carry out

data analytics. In accordance

with the Unity

Analytics terms

Unity Cloud

Diagnostics

(https://unity3d.com

/legal/privacy-policy)

United

States

Transmitted

from time to

time

Operating

system and

version, CPU,

graphic card

information,

system

language,

device model,

RAM, Unity

Player and

Unity Editor

versions, app ID

of game, screen

resolution

For diagnostics

purposes and

to ensure the

functionality of

the Game.

In accordance

with the Unity

Cloud

Diagnostics

terms

Hootsuite(https://w

ww.hootsuite.com/le

gal/general-data-

protection-

regulation)

Canada

Transmitted

from time to

time

Name, photos,

age, gender,

geographic

location,

opinions,

preferences,

and phone

numbers that

are provided or

posted by social

media users.

To manage

social media

platforms

centrally.

In accordance

with the

Hootsuite

terms

GameSight

(https://console.gam

esight.io/privacy-

policy)

United

States

Transmitted

from time to

time

Marketing

attribution data

To analyze the

performance

and marketing

efforts of the

Game.

In accordance

with the

GameSight

privacy policy

Data Destruction

Personal information is retained in accordance with the data retention periods as detailed in section

“Data Retention”. With the exception of the personal information set out below, personal

information, which has fulfilled the purpose for which it was collected or used, and has reached the

period of time during which personal information was to be possessed, will be destroyed in an

irreversible way. Personal information stored in electronic files will be deleted safely in an irreversible

way by using technical methods, and printed information will be destroyed by shredding or

incinerating such information.

The personal information detailed in section “Data Retention” are required to be retained pursuant

to the following laws:

Act on the Consumer

Protection in Electronic

Commerce, Etc.

Article 6 of the Act on the

Consumer Protection in

Electronic Commerce

In an electronic commerce or a mail-order

sale:

• Records regarding labelling and

advertising (6 months)

• Records regarding execution or

withdrawal of a contract (5 years)

• Records regarding the payment of a

price and the supply of goods and

services (5 years)

• Records regarding customer services or

dispute resolution (3 years)

Protection of

Communications Secrets

Act

Article 41 of the Decree of the

Act, Article 15-2 of the

Protection of Communications

Secrets Act

• Log records, IP address (3 months)

• The date of telecommunications by

users, the time that the

telecommunications start and end, the

frequency of use (12 months)

You may exercise rights related to the protection of personal information by requesting access to your

personal information or the correction, deletion or suspension of processing of your personal

information, etc. pursuant to applicable laws such as the Personal Information Protection Act (“PIPA”).

You may also exercise these rights through your legal guardian or someone who has been authorized

by you to exercise the right. However, in this case, you must submit a power of attorney to us in

accordance with the Enforcement Regulations of the PIPA.

You can also withdraw your consent or demand a suspension of the personal information processing

at any time.

Additional Use and Provision of Personal Information

In accordance with the PIPA, we may use or provide personal information within the scope of reason

ably related to the initial purpose of the collection, in consideration of whether disadvantages have

been caused to data subjects and whether necessary measures have been taken to secure such as en

cryption, etc. We will determine with due care whether to use or provide personal information in co

nsideration of general circumstances including relevant laws and regulations such as the PIPA, purpo

se of use or provision of personal information, how personal information will be used or provided, it

ems of personal information to be used or provided, matters to which data subjects provided consen

t or which were notified/disclosed to data subjects, impact on data subjects upon the use or provisio

n, and measures taken to protect subject information. Specific considerations are as follows:

• whether the additional use/provision is related to the initial purpose of the collection;

• whether the additional use/provision is foreseeable in light of the circumstances under which

personal information was collected and practices regarding processing;

• whether the additional use/provision unfairly infringe on the interests of the data subject; and

• whether the necessary security measures such as pseudonymization or encryption were taken.

Contact

To protect your personal information and handle complaints relating to your personal information,

we have appointed the following department responsible for managing and protecting your personal

information.

• Data Protection Department, responsible for the management and safety of your personal

information

• Email: privacy@10chambers.com
